warlordgames.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy • Warlord Games

**General Privacy**

By accessing and using this site, you hereby agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Warlord Games is committed to the protection of the privacy of its Website visitors.

On the site, we collect personal data in order to respond to your enquiries and may contact you via e-mail or phone. Personal data may include details such as your name, email address, telephone number, the best time to contact you, and any other information you wish to supply.

In addition to the personal information that you may provide us, this site may use technology that allows us to collect selected information regarding such technical aspects as your internet protocol address; your computer’s operating system; your browser type; traffic patterns and the address of any referring Websites.

We reserve the right to contact you from time to time to update you about anything of relevance happening with Warlord Games.

We may also occasionally email you promotional information, news articles or events relating to Warlord Games however if you would prefer not to receive such messages, you may unsubscribe by contacting us by email at **[info@warlordgames.com](mailto:info@warlordgames.com)**.

Web links from this site to external websites should not be construed as implying any relationship with and/or endorsement of the external site or it’s content by Warlord Games, nor any commercial or other relationship with the owners of such site.

You should be aware that these sites may have different privacy and security policies. We don’t have any control over them, and take no responsibility for information given to these sites.

Your satisfaction and privacy is a priority for us, so we take a number of steps to ensure your safety and to give you a pleasurable shopping experience with us. 

**E-mail Addresses**

We are aware of the annoyance of receiving junk e-mail. So, we want you to know that your e-mail address will **never** be given out or sold to any outside party, including ones that “you might be interested in”. This ensures that when you give your e-mail address to us for ordering, receiving our newsletter or account purposes, you will not receive any other e-mail resulting from that action. 

Our regular e-mails are limited to order confirmations, answers to your questions and the Warlord Games newsletter.

**Personal Information**

Any names or addresses provided will only be used by you, the customer, and by us here at Warlord Games for ordering or shipping purposes.. All personal data is collected and stored in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.

This policy will be reviewed periodically and updated versions will be posted here. If you have any questions regarding it please do not hesitate to conatact us at **[info@warlordgames.com](mailto:info@warlordgames.com)**

**EU Cookie Policy**

This site, like many others, uses small files called cookies to help customise your experience for a number of reasons and we presume “implied consent” if users visit the Warlord Games website and continue to use it after being informed about the cookies in operation outlined in our [cookie information page](http://www.warlordgames.com/home/cookie-information/):

Session cookies – allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browser session. They may be used for a variety of purposes such as remembering what a user has put in their shopping basket as they browse around a site. These session cookies expire after a browser session so would not be stored longer term. For this reason session cookies may sometimes be considered less privacy intrusive than persistent cookies.

For us these cookies are essential for the running of our websites. Without the use of these cookies parts of our websites would not function.

Persistent cookies – are stored on a users’ device in between browser sessions which allows the preferences or actions of the user across a site (or in some cases across different websites) to be remembered. Persistent cookies may be used for a variety of purposes including remembering users’ preferences.

We use functional cookies to remember your preferences on our websites. This is usually in conjunction with our webstore and forum.

First and third party cookies – Whether a cookie is ‘first’ or ‘third’ party refers to the website or domain placing the cookie. First party cookies in basic terms are cookies set by a website visited by the user – the website displayed in the URL window. Third party cookies are cookies that are set by a domain other than the one being visited by the user. If a user visits a website and a separate company sets a cookie through that website this would be a third party cookie.

We use these types of cookies to monitor our websites performance and how our users may use it. These cookies provide us with information that helps us provide a better product and also to identify any areas that may need maintenance.
